{
    "id": "d3b37e9727f8440ba13c89dc008c8d52",
    "title": "No, Not And None",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have ......................... time to talk to you now.",
            "description": "No is used with a noun to mean not any.",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0c0936f498b43838aea3630be97f305"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has answered ................................ of the questions.",
            "description": "We use none of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "none",
                "no one"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "68a5ff4f27904e1c979dc3947509f76f"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. matter what you say, I won't believe you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "None",
                "No one"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c6cf2cd88c8458ea3a46c69680f336e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ............................. fool.",
            "description": "This is a more emphatic way of saying 'She is not a fool.'",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "no",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "41827b4d451c491f8998298f2728f923"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. of the students participated in the program.",
            "description": "We use none of before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "None",
                "No",
                "Not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11eccfba614f4ff9a7c81e79877997a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. longer support the liberals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "no",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "515cd25fdede4962b57f2fc6eed90402"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for hours, but .............................. came.",
            "description": "No one means the same as nobody.",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "no one",
                "not one"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd028072ee9a447a8ae376e72a50f994"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. of them could solve the puzzle.",
            "description": "We use none of before a pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "No one",
                "None"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fca0565c099f468ab908485349dcd346"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. surprisingly, he failed the test.",
            "description": "We use not to make a word, clause or expression negative. ",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe439ea2e1064efe8554be42c6207d0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can come tomorrow, but ................................ on Monday.",
            "description": "We use not to make a word, clause or expression negative. ",
            "answers": [
                "no",
                "not",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb0d2f07c25a4370af58e7bdfced0efe"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ of the onlookers came forward to help him.",
            "description": "We use none of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "None",
                "Not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f4ca4355a7dd489ca059dd4a428e953d"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... doctors went on strike.",
            "description": "No is used with a noun to mean not any.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not",
                "None"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38ed0871b8c0433697896c7dcc150b2f"
        }
    ]
}